question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
